hey what's up everybody thanks for
listening to The Grow Your Life podcast
my name is Jeremiah Krakowski and on
this podcast I help coaches mentors
trainers and business owners scale their
business and make more money now today I
want to talk about how to make your
Facebook ads work I did a presentation
this weekend on this I'm going to
summarize it for you I think that this
is important for me to talk about
you can listen to this real quickly
wherever you're at and it's going to
help you right now we're sitting on the
couch here in my living room
um we just closed on a house this past
week super exciting we'll be moving at
the end of the month very excited for
that uh but what I want is I want to see
you making more money with your Facebook
ads and so here's the biggest thing that
stops people with their Facebook ads is
two things they over complicate the ads
manager itself
and they don't understand what actually
makes the ads work to produce results
okay so first off uh prior to 2018 when
Mark Zuckerberg appeared in Congress
they
made him they didn't make him but they
did make him like they they pretty much
forced his hand to change how ads were
done prior to that
like anybody could basically put up an
ad and get a ton of sales right away it
was it was freaky how easy it was to get
sales prior to 2018 and then that all
changed
and then cobit happened and this is why
specifically if you're a mentor if
you're a trainer Cove would happen
everybody popped on the scene with their
own course coaching program mentorship
online marketing the great resignation
all of that so lots of competition that
really hasn't died down a whole lot it's
just sort of ebb and flowed since covid
um I think that a lot of the people who
started around covid if they haven't
gotten success now they might have like
a second wave of it since we have some
economic hardship going on by the way
economic hardship inspires a lot of
mentors and coaches to pop on the scene
uh economic Prosperity
reduces the amount of them because a lot
of people can go get jobs elsewhere so
it's it's interesting Dynamic there but
with Facebook ads
iOS 14 happened in 2020
and that took away a lot of our
targeting options and so here's what a
lot of people don't get about targeting
their ads is the sales copy on the
landing page and then particularly video
ads more than anything else I've triple
and quadruple and
whatever is opal above quadruple
posted this again and again and again
and video ads are
Bar None the best way to attract the
right people to you the lead cost from a
video ad the cost of your ads results is
a little higher with a video ad but the
quality of the response is exponentially
greater in our experience and so
what you say in the video ad
what you write in the ad and then what
you write on the landing page where
people are signing up and particularly
if you're a mentor trainer or coach you
need to have people signing up on your
email list you need to put out free
offers or at the most if you're
marketing with ads like seven dollars
Seventeen dollar at the most maybe
twenty seven dollar offers because
beyond that I would Market to people the
more expensive stuff that are already on
your list are are already following you
at that point okay so that's one thing
to keep in mind is that when you're
marketing your ads you want to offer
free stuff to people on the ads and then
use that to attract the right clients to
you your sales copy itself
and the words you say in the video ad
and the words on the ad that's actually
what determines your targeting
and that's changed uh in the last five
six years completely changed
and so
what we do is like
you only want to be worried about broad
targeting and detailed targeting for
like 30 days
once you launch an offer because beyond
that you want to dial in what's called a
look-alike audience so a look-alike
audience is an artificial intelligence
AI audience
that
is based off of the actions and the
intent that people take on the algorithm
again listen if this sounds confusing I
kind of just threw at you the entire
strategy of how we run Facebook ads so I
get it might be a lot let's break it
down piece by piece here over the next
maybe 10 minutes and let me explain it
to you it's essentially two pieces you
gotta understand
and that's what I broke down in my
training this this past weekend this is
sort of like a summarized version of
what I broke down
because I'm not using it to sell you on
anything but plug though you know if you
want to join some of our free trainings
we are hosting a five-day intensive here
coming up
um if you're not in our accelerator
would love to have you join our
accelerator when we open the doors to
that our coaching program to help
mentors get more clients in their
business
um okay the two parts of Facebook ads
number one
the ads manager targeting building your
lookalike audiences okay this part is
actually way simpler than 99.9 percent
of people make it most people over
complicate this side of things
sales copy is the part we actually want
to put most of your energy and effort
and what's cool is now we use AI to do
this part of things which is awesome but
most people neglect actually doing this
part right and when they do it they miss
out on a lot of stuff if you watch back
through my podcast episode the last two
three months
a lot of times if I'm talking about
sales copy if I'm talking about
messaging I'm going to be talking about
you got to get very specific you have to
make bold promises you have to be
willing to put your your reputation on
the line and and go out there and
promise results to people because that's
really the only thing that's actually
going to get people to take action with
your ads otherwise they're just going to
ignore you because it's not important
enough to them to actually make the time
to prioritize even listening to you at
that point unless you are
bold with the promise that you're making
people and you want to make sure that
you're making promises specifically to
people that are going to get a result
with you that's number one but also just
as importantly are going to be a buyer
they're going to spend money with you
not everybody is a potential buyer so
understand that that with not everybody
being a potential buyer that's okay
um
because
if we look at the real world around us
like not everybody's gonna purchase
every product they see okay we're
getting inundated all the time with
products and services and messaging and
things like that
but just look at your own purchasing
habits
you buy products that because you fit
into a certain demographic and
psychological graphic
like how you think about the world your
world view your beliefs
and you buy certain products and
services because they fit into that for
the life that you want to live there's
people that you know could benefit from
the products you use every single day
the services you use every single day
but they just don't they either go with
the cheaper option an inferior option or
just a different option you know we got
Android and iPhone so you got to realize
that like not everybody's gonna be a
buyer of yours even if your product
could help everybody could everybody
benefit from from an iPhone of course
could everybody benefit from the
features of an Android that make it
better than an iPhone of course but
they're split like not everybody has but
both you get it so you got to understand
like that's how consumer behavior is
you're not going to change that when it
comes to your mentoring
so what we want to do is we want to lean
into consumer behavior of who is going
to be a buyer and who's going to
actually get results with us to create
case studies because you're not going to
convince somebody who's not a good fit
for working with you and a good fit is
defined by a lot of things again
you know a
uh
uh Android phone user
um
might
be a good fit for an iPhone user but
like they're like oil and water together
they're different types of people so
like like think about that like no but
like
you would really benefit from this
Android you're not going to convince
that Apple user
to change their mind and to suddenly
become this better fit for you right
does that make sense okay so that's
where a lot of people when it comes to
their mentoring when it comes to their
coaching when it comes to their
advertising they're literally trying to
do that the exact thing that I've just
talked about like they're trying to
convince an Apple user to use Android
and they're like but you could really
benefit from it so like understand that
it's way better worth your energy to
just focus on those people that love you
already that are resonating with you
that super are looking for they're
searching for they've been praying for
the thing that you've offered and lean
in with those people instead of trying
to convince anybody that they should
work with you that needs convincing
that's just not worth your time or
energy and it's not a way to build a
business trying to convince people
like it's just not okay so that's the
first side of it
then what you want to do is you want to
be able to Target those people with your
sales copy so the copy that you write
needs to focus in on the people
that are a good fit that will actually
end up buying something from you and
you're you're essentially going to leave
out the group of people that probably
isn't a good fit with you overall
so that's fine that's great that's what
is going to make more money when it
comes to the ads manager side of things
if you don't have an email list already
if you don't have a bunch of followers
if you don't have engagement on your
social media you start with broad
targeting we can ask chat GPT real
simply you know you could take your
sales letter or your offer and say okay
what's a group of people that I could
Target with this offer type it in and
it'll give you some options that you
could Target this is where people get it
wrong though okay hear me out
they end up spending
most of their time trying to dial in
that targeting
and then they're using that targeting
for their offers when they need to as
soon as they get
like 200 video views
200 people visiting their landing page
uh
200 people that are leads on their email
list you need to Pivot away from detail
targeting and go to lookalike audience
targeting to where the
the people are tracked
who actually took action with you and
then you build a bucket that's called a
look-alike audience and a look-alike
audience is an artificial intelligence
audience of people that are most similar
to those that already took an action
with you so automatically the detail
targeting is terrible now on Facebook it
really is we start with a broad range
chat GPT can give you some great ideas
as to who that is the target but the
prompt I use is you're a face I would I
would type this in the chat GPT you are
a Facebook ads expert who understands
detail targeting I'm wanting to promote
this offer and then I would paste your
whole landing page in there or at least
the top part of it
give me 20 options to try out for the
detailed targeting in the Facebook ads
manager and then you ask chat GPT to
give you that
only use that in the beginning when you
don't have people on your email list
when you don't have any engagement on
your social media if you have engagement
on your social media over the last six
months I would use that as a look-alike
audience because you can go into the ads
manager
put those people into a bucket and turn
it into a look-alike
and then Target those people with your
offers and then start to build better
look-alikes that stack on top of each
other based on the action that people
take it's kind of like a pyramid it's
like a reverse funnel okay so like the
quality goes up the higher the funnel
goes so if they're a lead that's a
better quality than somebody who just
engages with your content because they
gave you the name and email address
if somebody buys from you that's a
better quality than somebody who just
gave you their name and email address
and so we build our lookalike audiences
based off of these levels of intent and
action that people take and so then the
goal is all we do is we just send our
ads to the lookalike audience I
literally only send my ads to to one
look-alike audience for the last six
months to build our whole business we
did the same thing with Rick Pino we've
done the same thing for my mom one
look-alike audience based off of people
that are actually buying our programs
and then that look-alike audience
contains about 10 to 15 million people
that we Market our offers to so we're
lasered in with our targeting because of
the look-alike audience you can you can
have confidence in that the way you
build a good look like audience is with
your sales copy
so the algorithm decides who to show
your ad to based off of the words that
are in your ad and the words that are on
your landing page and so we use chat GPT
to put those words together very simply
very easily one of my favorite prompts
is this you could take your sales letter
and then this is the prompt that we'll
use convert the above to Pas copy and
then convert that to four Facebook ads
and I will literally use that
as our Facebook ads copy if you get my
chat gbt prompt document it's over at my
website it has a whole bunch of prompts
on it that you can use for your ads
the words that you put on your landing
page the words that you put in your
offer getting specific to a very
specific type of person
at a very specific stage in their life
Journey
with a very specific desired outcome
and qualifying them as not being a
certain group of people that is
disqualified or not a good fit or not
ultimately a buyer of yours laser
targeting in with the words that you use
on your sales copy
the robot algorithm and the AI Facebook
says actually has this meta AI
um department and they read what's on
the ad they they read the text in your
ad they read the words you say in your
video ads this is why graphic ads do not
convert as well as video ads as far as
the quality of people that you're
getting
ever they just don't
you got to be doing video ads we have a
chat GPT prompt to help you make video
ads
so the the algorithm will read what you
said in the video ad it'll read your ad
copy and it'll read the text on your
offer landing page that you're actually
sending people to and then that will
decide who they show your offer to who
they show your ad to so your targeting
is actually decided by
the copy that you write now so we create
these look-alike audiences of people
that are taking action
and then we dial our copy in around the
very specific person who's most likely
to buy from us and that brings our ads
cost down exponentially grows our sales
and that's exactly how in the last 12
months my wife and I have made a million
dollars in in our business
that's how we were able to help Rick
Pino make a million a month in his
business so my mom make over 20 million
dollars a year in her businesses
and and get a 36x return initially and
even on 80 and sometimes 100x return on
the back end those numbers are not
exaggerated by the way
when you follow this system of
advertising when you follow what we
teach you about sales copy about offers
for your mentorship business
80 to 100 times your ad spend is not
unreasonable
overall okay
and so
this this works
where people get stuck because they over
complicate the technical aspects of
their funnel
don't do that
they get stuck because they're they they
pre-record all the content that they're
going to sell don't do that pre-sell it
get some people in front of you let the
Q a and the feedback dictate what you're
going to Market to people
get all stuck on the tech aspects of the
ads manager don't do that
you could also hire somebody over at
onlinejobs.ph or Fiverr to help you set
up your pixel and the technical aspects
what's most important is putting an
offer out there to get people to sign up
on your email list and the best version
of those offers that we've found is is
live trainings
such as Zoom webinars we host Zoom
webinars a couple times a month and then
five day intensives or some people call
them challenges uh where you do a five
days in a row and you you you literally
provide a ton of value during your
webinar a ton of value during your five
day deal and then that's where you can
sell people on your program
and when you do this the the profit
margins are crazy
the profit margins are incredible the
community you build is incredible
okay so it's all about dialing in that
language one of the last keys I'm going
to give you as to how we dial that
language in is the feedback loop
so whenever we host a live event
whenever we host a webinar whenever we
host a five-day intensive whenever we
hope it's a challenge like that
we have people join a Facebook group and
there's questions in the group that we
ask them and this is actually one of the
most important parts of our entire
business
it's also one of the number one areas I
see people not doing
is
ask questions and the questions are what
are you struggling with in your business
what would you like to learn from us
and then people tell you in their own
words what they're dealing with we're
able to then feed that into the AI we're
able to feed their exact words into chat
gbt and it helps us dial in our offers
to laser in on the exact people that are
a good fit with us and then when you do
a like a live q a
or a VIP q a after your webinar that's
why we do those take the transcript of
that filter that into chat GPT pull out
the different nuances ask it what are
the pain points of the people from this
transcript what are their biggest
struggles what are their sacred cows
that they're trying to avoid what are
some areas of personal development that
would help them describe psychologically
what their biggest hindrances and blocks
are is there prompts that I asked chat
gbt all the time and it helps me
understand who I'm actually talking to
has helped me become a better Coach it's
helped me become a better Mentor it's
helped me if you've listened to this
podcast over the years really like get
better at how I teach overall and so I'd
love for you to join us if you're a
mentor if you're a coach if you're a
trainer and you want to make some money
and you want help in your business our
accelerators where you get to work with
me get my mind on your business to help
you grow and so get on the waiting list
for the accelerator join us for one of
our Live Events whether it be one of our
five day events I'm telling you people
tell us our five day intensive is worth
what they've paid ten thousand dollars
for before then I love that
join us for one of our our Saturday
webinars that we do uh people tell us
that those Saturday trainings are as are
as are as good as full courses that
they've invested in and so like I'm I'm
actually very proud of that fact that we
deliver so much value to people that
people are getting results that they're
seeing that their changes in their
business
um and and I want you to be one of the
next people that makes a ton of money in
your business as well all right so stay
connected with us share this podcast
with some people and we'll talk soon
grow your life
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]